http://www.absolutely-not-guilty.com/privacy

Contact Us
(404) 250-1113
Atlanta DUI AttorneysATTORNEYSThomas J. Thomas, EsquireAwards & AchievementsAttorney FeesDUI DEFENSEThe Ultimate Georgia DUI Law Fact SheetDUI LawsDUI Child Endangerment30-Day DUI RuleDUI Blood Test WarrantsGathering EvidenceFighting A DUIChoosing A DUI LawyerConsequences Of A DUIRisk Reduction ProgramHidden PenaltiesPrior DUI ConvictionsRestricted License and Limited PermitHardship License PlateDUI School & MADD Victim PanelPrice To Pay For a DUIFirst Time DUI2nd Time DUI3rd Time DUIFelony DUIDrug DUI’sPrescription Drug DUIField Sobriety TestsBreath Test DefensesOTHER PRACTICE AREASDrug DefenseDrug Distribution/TraffickingDrug ManufacturingDrug PossessionCocaineEcstasyHeroinMethamphetamineFelony DefenseForfeiture DefenseTheft DefenseTraffic OffensesWhite Collar DefenseCASE WINSTESTIMONIALSCONTACT USBLOG
(404) 250-1113
Home
/PrivacyPrivacyWhen you fill out our contact form on either the home page or our contact page we ask that you provide the following DUI case details:Your Name (required)Your Email (required)SubjectCase DetailsPhone Number (required)The information collected from you helps inform our free initial consultation process, which is usually conducted in our office. You may also contact us by email or by phone, in which case no data is stored on the site.How do we protect visitor information?We use an SSL certificate to provide encryption and authenticate that this site belongs to the Law Offices of Thomas J. Thomas, LLC. The web site ownership has been verified by Let’s Encrypt. For connection details, we suggest verifying the technical details in your browser. This website does not accept or store payment information from our clients. We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.Do we use ‘cookies’?We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf. It won’t affect the users experience if your browser does not support cookies.Third Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer personally identifiable information.Third party linksWe do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.GoogleWe have not enabled Google Adwords on our site.California Online Privacy Protection ActAccording to CalOPPA we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymouslyOnce this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it in the footer section of our web site.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page. Users are able to change their personal information:By emailing usBy calling usHow does our site handle do not track signals?We honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?We do not allow that.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)We do not specifically market to children under 13.Fair Information PracticesIn order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur we will notify the users via email within 7 business days.We agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.Contact InformationLaw Offices of Thomas J. Thomas, LLC750 Hammond Drive, Suite 5-100Atlanta, Georgia 30328thomas@absolutely-not-guilty.comPhone: (404) 250-1113This privacy statement was last updated on Friday, September 21, 2018.
Law Offices of Thomas J. Thomas, LLC
(404) 250-1113
Many people arrested for DUI feel as though they have already been pronounced guilty of a crime. If you have been charged with DUI, you should speak with expert DUI attorney Thomas J. Thomas.Office hoursMonday:
8:00 AM -
9:00 PMTuesday:
8:00 AM -
9:00 PMWednesday:
8:00 AM -
9:00 PMThursday:
8:00 AM -
9:00 PMFriday:
8:00 AM -
9:00 PMSaturday:
9:00 AM -
9:00 PMSunday:
12:00 PM -
9:00 PMPrice Range
Call for quoteAtlanta Office750 Hammond Dr. Building 10 Suite 200
Atlanta,
GA
30328
Recognition
PrivacyThe Law Offices of Thomas J. Thomas takes your privacy very seriously. Learn more.
